<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yilda Boukhtouchen</title>
    <link>https://yildab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yilda Boukhtouchen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 11:55:30 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yildab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>https://yildab.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:27:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yildab.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education Sept 2020 - Present MSc, Physics
Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, Kingston, ON
2020 BSc, Honours Mathematical Physics Minors in Pure Mathematics and Astrophysics
University of Waterloo, Waterloo, ON
Research Experience Sept 2020 - Present Queen&amp;rsquo;s High-Energy Astrophysics Theory (QHEAT) Group Member
Department of Physics, Astronomy, and Engineering Physics, Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, Kingston, ON
Graduate research assistantship, supervised by Dr. Joseph Bramante
Sept 2019 - Dec 2019 Exploring Quantum Entanglement in a Non-Local Game</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://yildab.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:26:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yildab.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a first-year Master&amp;rsquo;s student in physics and astronomy at Queen&amp;rsquo;s University. I am supervised by Dr. Joseph Bramante, within the Queen&amp;rsquo;s High Energy and Astroparticle Theory group (QHEAT), with research interests centring around dark matter phenomenology.
I graduated with a BSc in mathematical physics from the University of Waterloo in 2020, minoring in astrophysics and pure mathematics.
I am passionate about science outreach, especially programs aiming to promote interest in science to primary and secondary school students, as well as promoting diversity and inclusion in STEM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Article: Let&#39;s Talk Astrophysics Symposium</title>
      <link>https://yildab.github.io/posts/lta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 11:55:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yildab.github.io/posts/lta/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, the IDEAS Initiative in collaboration with Let&amp;rsquo;s Talk Science at Queen&amp;rsquo;s University ran Let&amp;rsquo;s Talk Astrophysics, a high school symposium about astrophysics. The event was incredibly successful, with over 300 unique participants. The symposium was aimed towards fostering Canadian high school students to have an interest in advancing into the natural sciences while exposing them to a maximally diverse set of volunteer physicists.
 - &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Talk Astrophysics Symposium&amp;rdquo;, departmental news article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2020: Year in Books</title>
      <link>https://yildab.github.io/posts/2020books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 15:05:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yildab.github.io/posts/2020books/</guid>
      <description>Just a list of novels I read in 2020. It was a good year for discovering high fantasy series!
  Oathbringer, Brandon Sanderson, The Stormlight Archive #3. ★ ★ ★ ★ ½
  The Lies of Locke Lamora, Scott Lynch, The Gentlemen Bastards #1. ★ ★ ★ ★ ★
  Red Seas Under Red Skies, Scott Lynch, The Gentlemen Bastards #2. ★ ★ ★ ★
  Le Roi de Fer, Maurice Druon, Les Rois Maudits #1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
